Hello, Ms. Choi.
Ms. Ryu, I'm just leaving now.
Do you know Ms. Cheon Sang-yeon,
by any chance?
- Cheon Sang-yeon of Swallow Pictures?
- Yes.
Yeah, I know her.
Who doesn't know Cheon Sang-yeon?
I mean, do you know her personally?
Personally?
A little. Ages ago.
It didn't seem like "a little, ages ago."
You didn't watch the Baeksang Arts Awards
last night, did you?
- No, I didn't.
- You should.
Watch Ms. Cheon's acceptance speech
for Special Achievements in Film.
Why? What did she say?
Hello. I'm Cheon Sang-yeon,
the CEO of Swallow Pictures.
Thank you.
All movies are the fruits of
the talent and passion of their creators.
If I, as a producer,
can claim any credit in the process,
I would like to gather all of that credit
and dedicate it to the person who's had
the greatest influence on my life.
My dear friend Ryu Eun-jung.
I want to thank you.
…had the greatest influence on my life.
My dear friend…
Ryu Eun-jung.
What a load of crap.
I hate that you're fine.
I want to see you ruined, like me.
YOU AND EVERYTHING ELSE
You severed ties?
Yes.
It's just
the expression "severed ties" is something
you only read about in books.
Why did you sever ties?
It's a long story.
Find anything good?
No.
I've been looking hard,
but no books have blown me away.
Me neither.
I've looked through
entire libraries lately,
but nothing has caught my eye.
Ms. Ryu.
What's the story behind
you and Ms. Cheon severing ties?
Would it work as a script?
Why not? You saying you severed ties
has me intrigued.
Thing is, there was no major incident.
It was just two girls bickering
until they decided to sever ties.
That's all there is to it.
But why did you sever ties?
Who knows?
How does it feel?
She said that you had
such a huge influence on her.
The Cheon Sang-yeon said such a thing.
Do you like Cheon Sang-yeon?
Well,
I don't dislike her.
Her company tends to make solid movies.
I wouldn't know.
I haven't seen any of them.
Even Echoes of Summer?
Okay, I guess I've seen that one.
Sounds like
you intentionally avoided them.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe I'm being petty
because she's too successful.
I guess I can't entirely deny it.
I don't think
Cheon Sang-yeon deserves the success.
Why not?
Do you remember my miniseries?
Yeong-won and Me.
The character Cha Yeong-won
was modeled after Cheon Sang-yeon.
I made her work in advertising,
but the rest is exactly what happened
with Echoes of Summer
Echoes of Summer?
You wrote that?
Yes.
Without that movie,
Swallow Pictures wouldn't exist today.
I developed that story.
Thinking about it
pisses me off all over again.
Shall we write a show about it?
- Rat her out to the world?
- Yes!
There's no major incident.
Of course there is. You severed ties!
And she stole Echoes of Summer.
Maybe you're right.
Actually…
I have written a little something.
About you and Ms. Cheon?
No, that's not it.
Do you remember last year
I told you that I wanted to write about
an elementary school teacher?
I'm warning you that it's a rough draft.
Start to finish,
it's just noisy elementary kids.
Just hand it over. Come on. Don't worry.
1992, FOURTH GRADE
FIRST DAY OF SECOND SEMESTER
ILYEONG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
CLASS SCHEDULE
Quiet!
RYU EUN-JUNG
Come in.
Twelve new kids transferred
in a single day.
Come in. Stand at the front.
- Attention. Salute.
- Good morning, sir.
Did you enjoy your break?
Yes!
You're not quite sure
what's going on, right?
Yes!
The kids who are absent today,
Sang-uk, Yong-don, Sang-beom, Jeong-ho,
Geun-su, Eun-i, Mi-jin,
Hyo-jin, and Shin-yeong,
all transferred
to a different school over break.
Did you see the new apartment complex
on your way to school?
Yes!
These kids have all moved
into those new apartments.
I'm Shin An-na
from Anyang East Elementary.
My name is Lee Ji-seon.
I'm Kim Jeong-ho.
I'm Seo Jeong-sik.
My hobby is playing the piano.
I'm good at arm wrestling.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
It's Sang-yeon's turn.
Come here. Everyone, listen up.
Hi, guys. I'm Cheon Sang-yeon,
transferring from Myeongjeong Elementary.
My mom told me that the "yeon" in my name
means "swallow."
Swallows are drifters,
so my dream is to be a deadbeat drifter.
She wants to be a deadbeat!
Sang-yeon's grandfather is rather famous.
He was once a government minister.
Whoa, cool!
Sang-yeon transferred here
from the best private school in Seoul,
and while there,
she was an outstanding student.
So our class has gained a great classmate.
Round of applause, everyone!
Wow!
I think Cheon Sang-yeon is a genius.
Really? How come?
In math, she had a contest
with our class president, Kim Kyeong-ho,
and she won!
- Guess what they worked on.
- What?
- A sixth-grade math question.
- A sixth-grade math question?
The teacher first gave them
a fourth-grade math problem…
I was subdued and silent at school,
but outside of school,
I became a total chatterbox.
He ended up giving them
a fifth-grade question.
- Thank you, sir.
- Bye, kids.
Wasn't your class also short on desks
because of the new kids?
We were three short. What about yours?
- We were two desks short.
- What did your class do?
Two of the new transfers don't have desks.
It would be nice
if someone volunteered to give up theirs.
The teacher asked the boys
if any of them would give up their seats,
and Kyeong-ho offered first.
- I will.
- I will!
Then all the other boys offered,
and the teacher decided…
Alrighty, then. Let's see who'll be
so kind as to give up their seats.
Let's see. Our volunteers will be
Go Yeong-rok and Lee Jeong-kyu!
What? Go Yeong-rok and Lee Jeong-kyu?
Even though Kyeong-ho offered first?
I already told you.
My teacher never makes
kids like Kyeong-ho do grunt work.
Just the kids from our neighborhood.
What did they do without desks?
To read large numbers,
we group the digits in sets of four.
Six, seven, eight, nine,
and two, three, four, five… like this.
Now label the first three digits
as thousands, hundreds, and tens.
The whole day?
The whole day. What about you guys?
We were all seated.
Yes, ma'am!
Now, listen up.
A mixture is when more than two matters
are blended together.
There are solid and liquid mixtures…
On the vaulting horse?
Yeah. The teacher and the class monitor
brought it to the classroom.
You're so lucky you have a nice teacher.
My teacher always plays favorites.
It's my mom. I'll catch you later. Mom!
Mom. Kim Mi-jin transferred schools.
Really? Where to?
I'm not sure. The teacher listed everyone
who transferred, including Mi-jin.
- But…
- Here, drink this.
For me? Again?
- I'm just so grateful.
- Thanks.
- Can I have the keys?
- The keys…
The keys… Here they are.
Thank you!
Mom.
Mi-jin didn't return my comic book
before transferring.
And?
And I'd borrowed it
from the truck bookstore man.
And?
I need to pay him for the comic book.
Can I have 1,700 won?
Is that why you followed me here?
Yes.
Don't you have any homework
now that school has started?
Twelve kids transferred to my class today.
- Twelve kids?
- Yeah.
There's this new kid
named Cheon Sang-yeon.
Apparently, her grandad was a minister.
That means he's high up, right?
High up, indeed.
What was he a minister of?
I don't know. Just a famous minister.
Mom, whose house is this? How come you're…
- Do you like it?
- Yeah.
The curtains are already up.
How pretty.
I have to work, so look around.
- I can look around?
- Why not?
That was the first time
I ever stepped inside an apartment.
That apartment
was spacious,
spacious,
and spacious.
It was just so spacious.
Mom! There's a bathroom
inside the bedroom!
And?
Not the one out there.
There's another bathroom in this room!
I know. This place has two bathrooms.
There are two bathrooms?
How can a single house have two bathrooms?
All these places do.
They all do?
Love at first sight.
- It was totally love at first sight.
- Mom.
- Who lives in places like these?
- Who knows?
The security guard says
it's a family of four,
so it's probably two children
and their parents.
Two children…
If you're bored,
why not help your mom out?
I'll give you 1,700 won.
Really?
YOU'RE SO LUCKY
On Saturday, there was a vote
for class president.
BALLOT
In a democracy,
who you vote for is a secret.
CHEON SANG-YEON
Cheon Sang-yeon.
SECOND SEMESTER CLASS PRESIDENT ELECTION
CHEON SANG-YEON, JEONG NAM-HYEON
Cheon Sang-yeon.
- Jeong Nam-hyeon.
- Huh?
Nam-hyeon, did you vote for yourself?
I did not!
- He totally voted for himself!
- He totally did!
When the teacher isn't here,
you're in charge.
Make sure the kids aren't chattering.
And if they don't listen to you,
you can hit them with this.
Kyeong-ho's right.
Who's in charge when I'm not here?
- The class president!
- Correct.
A round of applause.
I'll help you with this.
- Sorry?
- Hello. I'm the Seoul Milk lady.
That's quite all right.
Milk and newspaper delivery folks
promote sales like this,
so no pressure.
I just feel bad.
If you do, spare me
ten minutes of your time later.
You'll see it yourself,
but you don't need to clean
the sink and shelves.
I wiped everything down
with a sterile cloth.
When did you do all that?
Please be careful.
- Seventh floor, right?
- Yes.
You always let him have his way!
- Help me with this.
- Put everything inside.
How pretty. Is she your daughter?
Yes. She's upset
because she prefers her brother's room.
- What grade is she in?
- Fourth.
Ilyeong Elementary?
Yes. She made the transfer last week.
She wouldn't be in class five, would she?
Why do you ask?
The homeroom teacher is rather…
Why? What are they like?
I hear they treat children
based on their family's wealth.
One day, they were short on desks
because of the new transfers,
and the two poorest kids
were told to sit on the floor.
- For the entire day, no less.
- Oh dear.
How do you know such things?
My kid told me.
She must have thought it was unfair.
Your child must be smart. What's her name?
It's Eun-jung. Ryu Eun-jung.
Stop it.
Cut it out.
Keep it down.
- I told you to stop it.
- Hey, you.
Come up here.
It's just… Kim Hyeon-tae keeps kicking
my art project.
Kim Hyeon-tae too.
Me? But I didn't say anything.
Honestly, I wasn't trying to talk.
Kim Hyeon-tae kept kicking my project--
Ryu Eun-jung. If the class president
tells you to come up, you listen.
Would you talk back to the teacher?
Palms out.
- You too.
- I told you I didn't say anything.
She hits really hard.
Hey, Ryu Eun-jung.
Mommy's home.
Did you kids have a good day?
What's wrong?
Is something up?
No.
Let me see you.
So something is up!
I told you. It's nothing.
Who was it? Who upset my daughter?
Mom, the thing is,
earlier at school, Cheon Sang-yeon, she…
I was so upset and humiliated
by that incident
that I held a grudge for a very long time.
Even after we moved up a grade
and were put in separate classes,
just seeing Cheon Sang-yeon
triggered an urge to fight.
As my grades improved,
and I made more friends in fifth grade,
my personality changed.
Catch it!
Wait, time out! You stepped on the line.
- I didn't.
- Basically, I became cocky.
She stepped on the line right here.
- Let's just play.
- I didn't step on the line.
Hurry up.
Come on, try harder.
Throw it over here.
- Nice one.
- Catch it!
- Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
Are you all right?
Ryu Eun-jung!
Why did you aim for her head?
- She threw it at her on purpose.
- Why would I do that?
You've only been attacking Sang-yeon.
That's because Cheon Sang-yeon's good.
You were all attacking Eun-jung.
- It's dodgeball. People get hit.
- But she threw it at her head!
It really hurts to get hit in the head.
You can die!
- No, you can't.
- Yes, you can!
The teacher's here.
Everyone freeze.
Why are you fighting
instead of playing dodgeball?
You're here.
Hello.
Hi, Eun-jung.
It happened while playing dodgeball,
so Eun-jung should apologize.
Why don't you two shake hands and make up?
I'm sorry.
Class matches often get
a little out of hand.
Sang-yeon,
stop being dramatic and make up.
Admit that you did it on purpose.
- I didn't.
- As if!
You attacked me from the start.
It still wasn't on purpose.
You mean it wasn't intentional, right?
I didn't mean to throw it at her head.
Of course you did!
Cheon Sang-yeon.
You don't even know what happened.
She did it on purpose!
Cheon Sang-yeon.
Mom?
Yes?
Today,
we played dodgeball in gym class,
and I threw the ball at Sang-yeon.
It hit her head, so she went to the nurse.
To the nurse? How hard did you hit her?
I didn't hit her.
The ball did. It was dodgeball.
But
it did hit her hard.
Well, is she okay?
Yeah. She was all right soon after,
but I can't tell if I did it on purpose.
Even though I wasn't sure,
I denied it to the teacher.
Does that count as lying?
Who knows?
Are you really not sure?
Mom, Ms. Yoon came
to the nurse's office earlier.
My writing teacher.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I wonder why she was there at all.
What did she say?
She told Sang-yeon to make up with me,
but Sang-yeon talked back to her and left.
- She said, "You don't know what happened."
- Really?
She spoke rudely to the teacher?
Exactly.
- Move your legs.
- Don't touch me.
I don't know. I really don't.
- Write about it in your journal.
- I wouldn't know what to write.
Write that you don't know!
Tomorrow's Wednesday!
You have your extracurricular class.
THEME: THE MOST IMPORTANT PROMISE
I EVER MADE
For my extracurricular class,
I was in Ms. Yoon's writing class.
Now that I think about it,
my personality changed
on that day.
Raise your hand if you don't have a mom.
1 YEAR AGO
I'd wanted to cry that day
because that morning,
there had been a family background check.
No one.
Raise your hand if you don't have a dad.
- You don't live with your dad?
- I don't.
- Your name?
- Lee Han-jun.
Hey. You don't have a dad either.
He's only asking the new kids.
Anyone else without a dad?
Ryu Eun-jung doesn't have one!
She's always been at this school.
I'm just asking about the new transfers.
Let's move on to your parents' education
if there's no one else.
Whose parents only finished
elementary school?
- Goodbye.
- See you next class.
Goodbye.
Eun-jung?
Hello.
This is quite heavy.
Would you mind helping me?
Sure.
Thank you.
I was shocked that she knew my name.
Other teachers didn't know my name
because I was one of those kids
who blended in.
I was invisible.
All done!
You've been so helpful. Why don't you sit?
Okay.
Thank you for helping me.
Why don't you take off your bag?
Drink up.
Eun-jung.
You don't have a dad, do you?
No, I don't.
Are you shocked that I knew?
I was passing in the hallway
and happened to overhear.
My dad also passed away when I was young.
He passed away when I was in sixth grade.
How old were you when yours passed?
I was eight.
I see.
You must have been so heartbroken.
It was like that for me too.
I felt so sad whenever I missed my dad.
Do you feel the same?
Yes.
Thank you.
Go on and blow your nose.
Eun-jung.
I really wanted to tell you this.
Whether it's not having a dad or a mom,
it's sad not being able
to see the ones you love.
Yet, for some reason,
when I was younger,
I felt ashamed about not having a dad.
I didn't feel that way when I was alone,
but in front of others,
I think I felt embarrassed.
But now I think of it this way.
Look here.
This is the space
you hold in your heart for your dad.
Your dad's not with you now,
so it's empty, and that makes you sad.
Yes.
But it's up to you to decide
what to fill this space with.
If you, Eun-jung,
decide to fill this space
like this,
you could fill it up with goodness.
There. It's full.
Once you grow up, you can say,
"Not having a dad made me sad,
but I filled his space with these things,
which made me the person I am today."
Don't you think that would make your dad
proud as he looks down on you?
Yes.
On days when you're sad, write a journal.
Not the sort of journal
you write for homework,
but about how you really feel.
Okay.
Hand in your work if you're finished.
If not, finish it by tomorrow.
And don't forget to collect your journal
if you handed it in.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Park Yeon-jin?
Eun-jung?
Here.
- Next, Sang-hyeok.
- Thank you.
Bye.
TITLE: MY CONFUSED FEELINGS
You're right.
Our own feelings can be confusing.
Nevertheless, it's important to try
to understand your own feelings.
It's a rather exciting journey too.
One 500ml carton for apartment 1203.
One 500ml carton for 904.
One strawberry, one plain for 804.
A one-liter carton for 403.
- For 804--
- I know. It goes in the pouch.
- See you later.
- Okay.
SEOUL MILK
- Watch it.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- I'm sorry.
- You should be careful.
- What is it, Dad?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- You…
The kid's not to blame.
If you don't study,
that'll be your future.
It just had to be a day
when I had math class.
Math classes were split
according to your grades.
I was in the A class, so naturally,
Cheon Sang-yeon was too.
So what is a parallelogram?
It's a quadrilateral in which
both pairs of opposite sides are parallel.
If we call these parallel sides
the base sides of the parallelogram,
we can calculate the distance between…
Ryu Eun-jung,
I heard that you deliver milk.
What?
Who delivers what?
Ryu Eun-jung. She delivers milk.
- Is that true?
- No.
I don't. I was just helping my mom.
Yeah, by delivering milk.
Didn't you hear her say
she was helping her mom?
Kim Seong-kwon.
- He's in class one, isn't he?
- Yeah.
Why?
It was clear
that Cheon Sang-yeon had told him.
Cheon Sang-yeon was also in class one.
Why are you telling kids
that I deliver milk?
- I did?
- Yeah!
I helped my mom, who had hurt her leg.
Why would you start such a rumor?
I didn't start any rumors.
Then why is Seong-kwon from your class
teasing me about it?
How would I know? I didn't tell him.
I should ask you.
Why do you have it out for me?
- I do not.
- Admit it!
You attack only me in dodgeball.
You even hit me with the ball.
I didn't hit you.
It sure hurt.
- If it hurt, it means you hit me.
- You hit me first!
I did?
- When?
- In fourth grade!
You called me to the front
and hit me with the teacher's rod.
That was you?
Yeah, that was me, okay?
I wasn't chattering that day.
Kim Hyeon-tae kept goofing off.
Plus, my mom says it's ridiculous
for a student to hit another student.
Okay.
I get it.
If you're so upset, you can hit me too.
What?
I said hit me. Then we'd be even.
Hit me with this.
Hit me.
Do you think I won't?
I'm telling you to go ahead.
- You're seriously--
- Go on, hit me!
Hey, are you crying?
As if I'd cry!
- Why won't you hit me?
- Do you know how much this would hurt?
This is harder than wood.
You're the one who couldn't hit me,
so don't blame me.
You really didn't tell anyone?
I didn't.
Swear on it.
I swear.
Hey, Ryu Eun-jung!
You may not have hit me,
but I was already punished
for hitting you.
I didn't know it was you,
but my mom hit me
for hitting you that day.
My mom's Yoon Hyun-sook.
Ms. Yoon?
Yeah.
Mom, guess what.
Cheon Sang-yeon is Ms. Yoon's daughter.
Really?
Yeah. Last year, Ms. Yoon
was the homeroom teacher for--
I know. The homeroom teacher
for the class next to yours.
This year,
she teaches extracurricular classes.
Yeah. It turns out that
she's Cheon Sang-yeon's mom.
Really?
Hold up. Did you already know?
Yeah, I already knew.
How did you know?
She buys her milk from me.
It's hot. Move your hands.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
Was it you who told her I got hit?
Yeah.
I went to collect their milk money
and told her your class president hit you.
She was utterly shocked and apologized,
saying her daughter
is your class president.
Why didn't you tell me?
She told me not to.
She teaches the class next to yours
and no one at school
knows she's her daughter.
Don't tell the kids.
Okay.
Apparently,
Ms. Yoon hit Sang-yeon for hitting me.
- She did?
- Yes.
Cheon Sang-yeon's transferring next month.
Can't you be friends until then?
You want me to be friends
with Cheon Sang-yeon?
Yeah.
How tasty.
The thought of being friends
with Sang-yeon was so absurd
because Cheon Sang-yeon
was just too smart.
It was absurd
because she had such fair skin,
her grandad was a government minister,
and her mom, Ms. Yoon,
was my favorite teacher.
It was also because of Son Jun-ho,
my desk buddy.
Hey, Ryu Eun-jung.
Here.
Son Jun-ho was very popular.
Just this once. Please tell me.
Who does Son Jun-ho like?
I'm not sure, but I don't think it's you.
Still, deliver this to him.
- Go Na-mi told me to give you this.
- Go Na-mi?
If I'm honest, I liked Son Jun-ho too.
Do you guys want to choose desk buddies?
You'll soon be saying goodbye,
which is a shame.
Don't you guys want to?
Everyone in my class was keen.
We are too.
Let us choose our buddies, please!
- Yes, please.
- Please let us choose.
Okay.
- The process was simple.
- Jeong-sik?
Lee Eun-jae.
Boys would call out the name of the girl
they wanted to sit with,
and the girl would get the final say.
Seo Jeong-sik.
Jun-ho?
When it was Jun-ho's turn,
I was nervous for no reason.
It was obvious who he would pick.
Son Jun-ho would pick Cheon Sang-yeon.
Ryu Eun-jung.
Eun-jung?
- See you all in our next class.
- Thank you!
I could feel
the kids looking at me differently.
All of them except one.
- How could this happen?
- It's not a big deal.
Then Cheon Sang-yeon transferred
to the new school across from ours.
Can we talk?
What? A love letter?
Yeah. The day before she transferred,
Jun-ho wrote Sang-yeon a love letter.
I heard that he cried
while giving it to her.
He cried?
Because it's so tragic
to part with the one he loves.
- Right…
- Right?
Come on.
Now isn't the time
to be sitting here like this.
What else should I do?
Hey, Son Jun-ho!
Tell us the truth.
Did you really write Sang-yeon
a love letter?
- Sang-yeon?
- A love letter?
- The one who transferred?
- Really?
- What are you talking about?
- Is it true?
Do I have to answer?
Unbelievable.
Of course you have to answer!
If you wrote Sang-yeon a love letter,
it means that you like her.
Then why pick Ryu Eun-jung
as your desk buddy?
Because I wanted her as a desk buddy.
Why would you pick her as your buddy
when you like another girl?
- Eun-jung really likes you.
- I never said that.
But you wrote Sang-yeon a love letter!
You acting like that is confusing girls.
That means you're two-timing!
- Two-timing?
- Why are you yelling in our classroom?
You stay out of it!
Why should I? He says he wanted
to sit with her. What's the big deal?
Incredible.
- Why did you want to sit with Eun-jung?
- Because she's easy to be around.
She was already my desk buddy,
so I was comfortable with her.
That means you didn't pick her
because you liked her!
So you picked her
because she was an easy choice?
So what if she was an easy choice?
Why are you overreacting?
What did you say? Overreacting?
How dare you!
You think Eun-jung's a pushover?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hi, girls.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Wait, Eun-jung?
Under the TV. Second drawer…
It felt strange.
It was all quite strange.
It's not like I hadn't known that
Sang-yeon was Ms. Yoon's daughter,
but I felt deflated,
as though I'd just found out.
Complete.
Being there, Sang-yeon appeared
complete.
Entirely out of reach,
like somebody I could never beat.
It was that house.
There.
Cheon Sang-yeon was the one
who lived there.
YOU'RE SO LUCKY
Who are you?
Who… are you?
I'm, well… Ryu Eun-jung.
This short middle school kid would,
three years later,
become my first love.
Let's do this, Ms. Ryu.
How can you say that
after reading a mere draft?
Yes, it's a draft,
but I think it'll be good.
You do?
It does feel nice to hear that from you.
Why did you stop writing here?
Things were getting juicy.
It should write itself.
I guess something stopped me.
I must have forgotten
that writing about those times
would mean talking about Sang-hak oppa.
Why? You can't talk about him?
It's not that I can't.
This person named Sang-hak.
He's Ms. Cheon's brother, right?
Is it uncomfortable for you
to write about him?
Why? How intense
was this first love of yours?
If it was three years later,
you'd only have been in eighth grade.
I guess so.
Either way,
he had a huge influence on me.
Just write it.
I don't know this number. Who could it be?
Don't mind me.
Hello?
Yes, this is she. Who's calling?
Sang-yeon?
Cheon?
Right. One second.
Was it really Ms. Cheon?
I guess so.
What did she say?
She wants to meet.
She needs to tell me something.
Tell you what?
Maybe she wants to offer you a project.
Everyone from film production
is moving over to series these days.
It's been a while.
Why did you call?
It's just
you seemed so frigid.
I remember when I'd use my mom
as an excuse.
Back in the day,
whenever you were mad at me,
I'd bring up my mom,
and it would soften you up
and make you agree to anything.
I've been practicing
what I wanted to say to you today,
but now that I'm here,
I can't get the words out.
Just say it.
Apparently, I'm dying.
What?
I'm only 43 years old.
Are you
ill?
Cancer.
It's terminal.
It's unbelievable, isn't it?
I feel the same way.
Hang on a minute.
I have a favor to ask you.
What is this?
Keep looking.
That's right.
They've made films about it,
so you might know
about assisted dying.
I know it's not an easy ask…
but I really hope you'll help me.
Won't you
come with me?
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi